<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="category_places">Places</string>

    <string name="category_restaurants">Food</string>

    <string name="category_monuments">Monument</string>

    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="description_nikes_art_center">Nike’s centers aren’t classrooms.
        They are workshops where Nigerian artists and craftsmen ply their trades. There is no
        syllabus, no course of study. You decide what you would like to study or try, and then
        apprentice yourself to someone, or find a teacher. The textile artists, painters, sculptors,
        dancers and drummers are proud of their achievements and happy to share their knowledge with
        you.
    </string>

    <string name="description_national_museum">The Nigerian National Museum was founded by the English
        archaeologist Kenneth Murray. The museum has an eminent accumulation of Nigerian workmanship,
        including bits of statuary and carvings and archaeological and ethnographic displays. You
        can find galleries dedicated to the Nok Terracottas from Benin City, the bullet-riddled car
        from the assassination of Murtala Muhammed, carved ivory, ancient royal crowns and intricate
        handcrafted artefacts from all over Nigeria.
    </string>

    <string name="description_new_afrika_shrine">The New Afrika Shrine is an open air entertainment
        centre located in Ikeja, Lagos State. It serves as the host location of the annual
        Felabration music festival. Currently managed by Femi Kuti (eldest son of Fela Kuti)
        and Yeni Anikulapo-Kuti, it is the replacement of the old Afrika Shrine created in 1970 by
        Fela Kuti until it was burnt down in 1977. The New Afrika Shrine showcases photo galleries
        of Fela and music performances by Femi Kuti and Seun Kuti thus making it a tourist attraction.
        On July 3rd, 2018, French President Emmanuel Macron visited the Shrine and pre-launched the
        Season of African Cultures 2020 in France. Macron said he had visited the Shrine as a
        student in 2002.
    </string>

    <string name="description_scoan">The Synagogue, Church of All Nations (SCOAN). According to the
        organisation, more than 15,000 members attend its weekly Sunday service; visitors from
        outside Nigeria are accommodated in the accommodation blocks constructed at the church.
        The Guardian reported that The SCOAN attracts more weekly attendees than the combined number
        of visitors to Buckingham Palace and the Tower of London.
        with thousands of foreigners flocking to attend the church\'s weekly services. Figures
        released by the Nigerian Immigration Service indicated that six out of every ten foreign
        travellers coming into Nigeria are bound for the SCOAN.
    </string>

    <string name="description_terra_kulture">Terra Kulture Arts and Studios Limited is an educational
        and recreational organization set up in 2003 to promote the richness and diversity of
        Nigerian languages, arts and culture. Mrs. Bolanle Austen-Peters has an abiding passion and
        respect for all cultures and observed that there were few institutions effectively supporting
        Nigerian culture. There were, and remain, few places in Nigeria with the appropriate ambience
        for Nigerians and foreigners to learn about Nigeria’s cultural and linguistic heritage.
    </string>

    <string name="description_icm">Ikeja City Mall comprises 23,000 square meter of A-grade retail
        space in Ikeja, a suburb of the city of Lagos and the capital of the state, ICM is an
        ultra-modern Shopping Centre in what is described as a dual economic state;
        residential but predominantly commercial. ICM is the choice retail destination in Lagos with
        a wide selection of national and international tenants. The total 23,000 square meters area
        of ICM guarantees ample parking space for shoppers.
    </string>

    <string name="description_quilox">Club Quilox is a luxurious style nightclub in Victoria Island,
        Lagos owned by Shina Peller. Housed in a massive building, Club Quilox also operates a
        restaurant and bar. It opened in 2013, as one of the biggest and most expensive nightclubs
        in Nigeria.
    </string>

    <string name="description_hard_rock_cafe">Hard Rock Cafe is one of the classic restaurants in
        Lagos, with a different mouthwatering menu that would give your taste bud another feeling.
        Their menu prices are not too expensive but still affordable. You can get them in Abuja and
        also in Lagos. To set up a date with them they are on Instagram where you can keep a tab on
        them.
    </string>

    <string name="description_shiro"><![CDATA[Shiro possesses a surreal glow ensuring that you will
    never be able to ignore your surroundings. The mood starts cool and chic but transforms, as the
    night unfolds, yet, you can find intimate corners to dine or simply chill at any time. An
    organic, blend of cuisines, culture & service from all over Asia mixed with a unique blend of
    western music & signature cocktails, Shiro is the ultimate dining or late night experience.]]>
    </string>

    <string name="description_talindo">Talindo Steak House has been around for years and is still
        going strong. They have fantastic steak, Italian dishes and how can we forget the sizzling
        brownies, and their newest gourmet creation, the yummy apple pie. The intimate decor and
        friendly service make Talindo a strong favorite.
    </string>

    <string name="description_lafric">L\'afric is a great place to eat delicious African cuisines
        all in a  traditional yet sopisticated way.The restaurants boasts of a cool ambiance,nice
        decor as well as well mannered customer service. If you crave a healthy African dish in a
        sophisticated way yet with large healthy servings and staff that wouldn\'t hesitate to pack
        your food up as take away if you happen not to finish it,then L\'afric restaurant is the
        right restaurant.
    </string>

    <string name="description_sailors_lounge">Sailor\'s Lounge brandishes itself as the best
        Bar/restaurant in Lekki Phase 1, Lagos Nigeria,  a cool spot to hangout with friends
        and family, Sailors Lounge is the place to be. Meals range from seafood to poultry and beef.
        Mainly continental dishes. Alongside catfish peppersoup and grilled catfish.
    </string>

    <string name="description_oceans_basket">Ocean Basket is South Africa\'s favourite chain of
        seafood restaurants. There\'s one near you. At Ocean Basket you\'ll find friendly people,
        a home-from-home feeling and great value for your hard-earned bucks. Some Ocean Baskets
        have a fresh-fish deli too, and you can order to eat in or takeaway, whatever grabs you.
    </string>

    <string name="description_craft_gourmet">Something about Craft Gourmet Lagos by Lou Baker will
        remind you of the Ladurée café in Harrods. It feels just as charming. The white open space,
        simple decor, abundance of light, and the menu lets you see straight through the philosophy
        of the place which is perhaps to keep things simple, tasteful, and delicious. The staff are
        friendly and attentive. The whole place feels like a breath of fresh air in a part of
        Victoria Island that is otherwise choked up. It’s also entirely possible that when you go
        there, you will find yourself surrounded by french speaking people and then you will really
        feel the magic. After all, who doesn’t love a little bit of Francais?
    </string>

    <string name="description_arabesque">Arguably the best Middle Eastern restaurant in Lagos, this
        is a great environment to come over with family and friends and enjoy the picturesque
        environment, great food and lovely company. This is a Lebanese restaurant serving incredibly
        delicious Mid Eastern dishes in an environment that is entirely out-of-Lagos. It\'s like a
        journey around Middle East in term of ambiance, food, and believe me it\'s amazing.
    </string>

    <string name="description_casper_gambini"><![CDATA[Crafted by international chefs and tailored
    according to every country’s special taste, our menus will bedazzle you wherever you
    decide to pay us a visit. Get the chance to experience the genuine taste of our creations in
    different countries of the world.  Whether you decided to pass by for breakfast and a cup of our
    award winning coffee, for lunch, dinner, or even for an organic tea accompanied with signature
    desserts with friends, family, or loved ones, you will always find a reason to visit Casper &
    Gambini’s!]]>
    </string>

    <string name="description_freedom_park">Freedom Park is a memorial and leisure park area in the
        middle of downtown Lagos in Lagos Island, Nigeria which was formerly Her Majesty\'s Broad
        Street Prison. It was designed by the Architect Theo Lawson.  The Park was constructed to
        preserve the history and cultural heritage of Nigerians. Monuments in the park reveal the
        Lagos colonial heritage and history of Her Majesty\'s Broad Street prisons. It was built to
        commemorate the 50th anniversary independence celebration in October, 2010. The Park serves
        as a National Memorial, a Historical landmark, a Cultural site, Arts and Recreation centre.
    </string>

    <string name="description_mko_abiola">The MKO Abiola Statue was designed and erected by
        Olurotimi Ajayi in memory of Chief Moshood Abiola, a politician who was widely regarded as
        the winner of the inconclusive 1993 Nigerian elections. Standing at about 46 feet
        tall, the statue was unveiled on 12 June 2018 during the administration of Governor
        Akinwunmi Ambode.
    </string>

    <string name="description_queen_amina">Queen Amina Statue is an equestrian statue in honour of
        Queen Amina, an Hausa Warrior Queen of Zazzau. The sculpture was originally designed by Ben
        Ekanem in 1975 during the Second World Black and African Festival of Arts and Culture and
        was placed at the entrance of the National Arts Theatre in Lagos State. It was destroyed in
        2005 due to weathering but was however re-designed in 2014 by an unsigned artist.
    </string>

    <string name="description_shitta_bey">Shitta-Bey Mosque is a mosque, religious learning centre
        and one of the oldest mosques in Nigeria. The mosque is located at Martins Ereko Street,
        Lagos Island, Lagos, Nigeria. It was established in 1892 and designated as National monument
        by Nigerian Commission for Museums and Monuments in 2013. The mosque, considered one of the
        most important historical legacies of Nigeria, was named after its founder Sierra Leonean-born
        Nigerian, Mohammed Shitta Bey, who was an aristocrat, philanthropist and businessman.
    </string>

    <string name="description_tafawa_balewa_square">The Tafawa Balewa Square, (TBS) is a 14.5-hectare
        (35.8-acre) ceremonial ground (originally called \"Race Course\") in Lagos Island, Lagos.
        Lagos Race Course now Tafawa Balewa Square, was a sports field that hosted horse racing, but
        included a section for football and ground to play cricket. The land was provided to colonial
        authorities by Oba Dosunmu in 1859, who thereafter, built up the surrounding areas. The course
        was later demolished by the government of Yakubu Gowon to make way for Tafawa Balewa Square.
        In its hey days, the course hosted the Empire Day parades. The horse racing track was about
        seven to eight furlongs or a mile. In 1960, the course was redeveloped to celebrate Nigeria\'s
        independence and the lowering of the union jack.
    </string>

    <string name="description_tinubu_square">Tinubu Square (formerly Independence Square), is an
        open space landmark located in Broad Street, Lagos Island, Lagos State, Nigeria. It used to
        be called Ita Tinubu in memory of Madam Efunroye Tinubu, a slave trader and business magnate,
        before it was named Independence Square by leaders of the First Republic and subsequently
        Tinubu Square.
    </string>

    <string name="details">more</string>

    <string name="description_lekki_conservation">Lekki Conservation Centre (LCC) is a 78-hectare
        (190-acre) Natural Resource Conservation in Lekki, Lagos State. The centre was established
        in 1990 to serve as biodiversity conservation icon and environment education centre. The
        facility was built by the Chevron Corporation for the Nigerian Conservation Foundation (NCF),
        as a reserved sanctuary for the rich flora and fauna of the Lekki Peninsula. The company has
        since provided annual funding for the management of the centre.
    </string>

    <string name="description_tarkwa_bay">Tarkwa Bay is an artificial sheltered beach located near
        the Lagos harbour in Nigeria. Due to its island status, it is only accessible by boat or
        water taxis. The beach, popular with swimmers and water-sports enthusiasts, also has a
        welcoming resident community. There are several parts of Lagos Island where you can board a
        ferry or high-speed boat to the bay. The most popular places to get a boat to Tarkwa Bay are
        Marina, Mekwe Jetty, and Tarzan Marine (Victoria Island).
    </string>

    <string name="description_atican">Atican Beach Resort is a serene and scenic private beach resort
        located in Lekki-Ajah, Lagos. The resort perfect for various leisure and relaxation
        activities. Explore the selection of Caribbean styled beach huts that lie along the ocean
        coastline. The resort is an ideal destination for family trips and romantic getaways with
        your partner. It is also perfect for corporate retreats and bonding with friends.
    </string>

    <string name="lufasi">Lufasi Nature Park covers a large area of about 20 hectares of land at the
        Majek area (Km 41) along the Lekki-Epe Express Way. The park is home to species like the
        Ekki “Iron Wood” tree (Lophira Alata), the endangered Hooded Vulture (Necrosyrtes Monachus)
        and the African Pied Hornbill (Tockus fasciatus). The vegetation consists of pocket habitats
        of swamp forest and oil-palm plantation with large garden spaces and pond-side landscapes for
        recreation and celebrations. Lufasi Nature Park aims to help conserve native biodiversity,
        educate about Climate Change and the natural environment, and collaborate with the wider
        community of stakeholders.
    </string>

    <string name="description_greenfingers">An initiative in Lagos helping kids learn about the
        environment through a small zoo where they can see the country\'s flora and fauna. Another
        project teaches how to use plastic as resource to create something new.
    </string>

    <string name="lekki_leisure_lake"><![CDATA[Lekki Leisure Lake is located along the Lekki
    Peninsular in Lagos overlooking the Atlantic. Lekki Leisure Lake is the best destination for
    safe, authentic outdoor fun in Lagos. Tucked away along the Lekki peninsula shoreline, the
    resort’s cool tranquil lake is host to thrilling aquatic attractions including jet skiing and
    other exciting watercraft activities.  The Lekki Leisure Lake is a safe & seaside activity
    centre where kids & adults can indulge themselves in thrilling & adventurous activities like
    quad bikes, jet skis, wave boat, pontoon boat, pedal boats. If you are supposed to have any
    private function then Lekki Leisure Lake is going to be worth spending money.]]>
    </string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>

</resources>
